Why?
Because it would not
occur to you why.
Blushing suits you.
- Lord... I'm sorry.
- It's nothing to be sorry about.
No. this whole thing...
The whole idea is preposterous.
I don't think so.
- You sure you don't need glasses?
- I'm a pilot.
My vision is pefrect.
(Jake) What are we getting?
(Michael) Nine knots.
Shit! We should be keeping up.
- You sure the throttle's open?
- Wide open.
Come on. you overgrown goldfish!
Come to Uncle Jake.
- How long have you known Hoagie?
- What?
How long have you known Hoagie?
- What's he got to do with it?
- How long?
Since he got here.
Bring it to starboard!
When did he get here?
- Who?
- Hoagie!
Christ!
0ne day he was just here. that's all.
(Michael) What do you know about him?
He's after my mother.
- What's so funny?
- He's not good enough for her. eh?
I agree. I'd send her home right now.
Bring her about.
we're going the wrong way.
I mean. some of these pilots
are flying drugs down here.
- He's always going off somewhere.
- Bring her about. now!
- I am!
- Hurry. man. we're losir him!
- You must know something.
- Christ!
He likes gambling.
he likes women. don't bother me!
- He flies charter...
- Damn! We lost him!
Maybe your gear crapped out.
Maybe you crapped out.
flappir your lips about Hoagie.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Maybe he's gone.
All right. Mr Fish.
We'll come back and find you
tomorrow.
All he did was kiss me!
- (Carla) Well. that's a beginning.
- A beginning of what?
To whatever happens next.
0h.
I used to think I could handle these
situations once I was grown up.
but I don't even know
if he's serious.
Mmm. give it some time. Ellen.
See what happens.
Well. part of me wanted to
go off with him.
I couldn't.
I don't know why he wants me.
Maybe he's got good taste.
He hasn't spent
much time with a woman like you.
I don't know what he thinks.
0r what I think. This is so silly!
I feel too old to be in this thing.
I hope not. I am counting on
a long. happy sex life.
(Both chuckle)
(Creaking)
You said it wasrt polite
to interrupt people.
Yes. I did.
- It's time for tea. Grandma.
- 0h. I almost forgot.
I didn't.
I put everything in my room.
My teddy bear's joining us.
(Ellen laughs)
(Gasps)
Michael?
Michael. what is it?
Nothing. just a stupid dream.
Hmm.
(Sighs)
Time for bed. peanut.
- 0h. no!
- Yep. Daddy's got homework.
- But you let me last night.
- Yeah. yeah.
Mommy's waiting to read a story.
- Good night. sweetheart!
- Good night.
Night. Let's put up our feet
and shoot the breeze.
or whatever it is beer drinkers do.
I. uh. I got to put
together this report. Ma.
Jake says don't do today
what you can put off tomorrow.
Yeah. Jake's got a lot of those.
I'm leaving in a few days.
I don't want to go with you unappy.
I'm not unappy.
I saw you and Thea.
You looked just like your father.
Do you remember when
you guys used to imitate him?
Mom. I gotta get this finished. 0K?
- I worry about you.
- There's nothing to worry about.
I'm your mother. It's my job.
Just cos you're a man
doesn't mean I've retired.
I've worked on MY smile.
It's... it's your turn.
That's better.
(Jake on radio)
'Blump. blump! Blump. blump!
- 'Blump. blump! Blump. blump! '
- Jake. knock it off!
Blump. blump. 0K.
just don't try to renege on our deal.
Half a day on the snails.
then a half a day on the shark.
You got 17 more minutes. then we're
gonna go look for that shark.
(Michael) It's a big ocean. We could
spend the rest of our lives looking.
'We're gonna find him.'
'I got about a half a dozen.
I'll tag 'em and be right up.
'You. uh. hearir anything? '
Nothir at all. Just another cool.
calm. tickly day in the Bahamas.
Just stay within a quarter mile.
I got a three-mile monitor radius.
Within three miles. there's plenty of
time to beam your ugly ass up.
(Electronic heartbeat)
Michael. I got him.
'He's comir towards you.
You better get out now.'
All right. I'm comir. I'm comir.
(Monitor beat quickens)
Shit!
Jake!
Michael! Michael!
'Michael! '
Michael. what's goir on?
Michael. can you hear me?
'Michael! Michael. can you hear me? '
(Grunting)
(Breathing fast)
Michael!
(Panting)
(Latch creaking)
(Grunting)
Son of a bitch! 0h. shit!
Jesus Christ!
(Metal clanging)
Ah!
(Gurgling and gasping)
Uh!
(Jake) It's over there!
Shit! Get the bang sticks.
we're goir down.
- They're no good.
- Get another one!
(Grunting and panting)
(Jake) Come on. come on! Michael!
- Get him up! Watch his arm!
- (Clarence) Lay him down gently!
(Jake) We need a tourniquet
to stop his bleeding.
- (William) Try this!
- Get the wet suit off.
(Jake) Keep cool. don't worry.
(William) Michael. how are you?
I think he may be in shock.
(Jake) Clarence. move it!
Hey. hey. hey!
Hey. what you doir. man?
No one goes in the water
till we know where that fish is.
You fall off the horse.
you get right back on.
Hell. what kind of bullcrap
you talkir? Huh?
- Anybody's in the water. it's me.
- Jake. I'm gonna go down.
All right. so what about Carla's gig?
It's almost time. man.
Michael. I can't just let you
go back down.
I'm scared shitless.
What the hell do I do
if I can't go back in that water?
All right. be careful.
Clarence. get up on that shack.
Give us some lookout.
- I hope he knows what he's doing.
- He's doir what he's got to do.
Jake. are you gettir
anything on the shark?
No. everything's cool.
I'm thinkir about yesterday.
It's probably a mistake.
- He was hungry. You look tasty.
- But how come only me?
- Maybe he just like white meat.
- You're a funny guy. Jake.
Jesus!
(Laughter and applause)
(Man) It is about art
that I wish to speak today.
The raw material of art
surrounds us all.
catching in the net that each
and every one of us casts
into the current of life.
- But it takes the art...
- Where the hell are they?
They'll be here.
- Can I go on the banana boat?
- Shh!
Margaret's going.
She's with her mother.
- 0K.
- 0h. boy! 0h. boy!
- Thea. you be careful.
- I will. I will!
- (Ellen) Thea!
- It's 0K. Banana boats are fun.
0h. we should be so lucky.
I wish we were out with her playir.
Margaret. wait for me!
'Get to the point. man.'
as my wife now says.
(Laughter and applause)
0K. Well. in short. art is grease
for the wheel of life.
Today we are privileged
to dedicate a work of art.
Carla Brody.
an artist of growing reputation.
was commissioned to express
our way of life in permanent form...
to show the world what we all know
right here on this beach:
That it is better in the Bahamas.
- (Woman) Absolutely.
- Ladies and gentlemen. Carla Brody!
Thank you. Commissioner Witherspoon.
Mrs Witherspoon.
Thea!
0h. my God!
Stop! Come back! Bring her back!
(Screaming)
Stop! Thea! Thea!
Thea!
Somebody do something!
0h. no! My God!
- Mommy! Mommy!
- Thea!
(Man) Somebody get a doctor!
Get a doctor now!
(Man) Quickly!
(Engine revs)
- I'm sorry I missed you.
- Where have you been?
What's the matter? What happened?
Thea was attacked by a shark.
0h. my God.
The doctor said she should be 0K.
She's in shock.
Sweetheart? Sweetheart?
I'm so sorry.
I should've known. Jesus.
Should've known what?
- We tried to keep track of him.
- 0f...
The shark.
- You knew?
- Yeah. Thought it went away.
- Came after me.
- She could've been killed. You knew?
And you didn't tell us?
You let your mother think...
Where is she?
- How could you do that?
- Where's my mother?
- Why didn't you tell us?
- Where's Jake?
- WHY DIDN'T Y0U TELL US?
(Carla) Michael!
Jake!
- Jake!
- What?
Come on! I need you! Hurry up!
Hoagie! Did you see our boat?
- (Hoagie) I just got here.
- My mother took it.
- I hope she's a good sailor.
- A shark attacked Thea.
She went after the damn thing.
- She's gone after it?
- Yeah. we gotta stop her.
In that?
It'll take all day in that bathtub.
Got a better idea?
I'll radio her position.
The rescue boats will pick her up.
so don't worry.
She'll be fine.
She'll never find that bloody shark.
We couldn't.
(Michael) It'll find her.
(Jake) What do you mean?
She said it was coming.
- What do you mean?
- What do you know?
She thinks the shark
that killed Martin and Sean
is following the family.
Hey. he's not talkir
about our shark. eh?
What do you do when
you're not flying people?
I deliver laundry.
(Hoagie) Hold on. What's that?
Let's have a look.
0h.
(Hoagie) It's a big ocean out there.
(Michael)
Can't this thing go any faster?
Any faster. this thing'll be
a flying Cuisinart
and we'll be diced into oblivion.
Come and get me.
you son of a bitch.
There she is.
That's her right there.
Is that what I think it is?
- Mom...
- Hold on!
0h!
(Hoagie) 'Thomas. you there?
This is Zero-Papa-Alpha here.'
(Man on radio)
'Hoagie. where are you? '
12 miles southeast of Emerald Key.
Look for Neptune's Folly.'
I need two boats fast and somebody
who can kill a shark - a big one.
(Man) 'What're you doing? '
(Hoagie) Practising landing.
Hang on to your socks. lads.
Wait! You sure you know
how to do this?
0f course not!
What kind of pilot do you think I am?
- Christ!
- Hell. not half bad.
Get out. I'll keep it busy.
No. it'll come for the plane's
electromagnetic impulse.
(Hoagie) Get the bloody hell out!
Michael!
Damn passengers! You're all the same.
Complain. complain...
0h. shit!
Hoagie!
Hoagie! Hoagie!
Why'd you come out here?
- Why did you bring him?
- Mom. Mom!
- Why'd you take the boat?
- It kept coming!
- Didrt you realise?
- There was nothing else to do.
- You shouldn't have done it.
- I tried to tell you.
I tried. (Sobbing)
(Hoagie) Hey!
Give me a hand. for Christ's sake!
- Hoagie!
- How the hell did you do that. man?
- It wasrt easy. believe me.
- Get him up.
(Grunting)
(Jake) You all right. man?
- 0h! Bloody hell.
- (Jake) Get it started!
- The breath on that thing!
- You are alive!
Let's get out of here.
Ellen Brody. 0h!
Good. this thing's still working.
(Engine spluttering)
That's your engine. pal.
I'll have a look.
(Electronic beating)
0h. shit. he's close. man.
- What is that sound?
- The shark's heartbeat.
Hoagie. try to finish.
Michael. gimme a hand. I got an idea.
We're taking water down here.
Ellen. start pumping here.
(Hoagie) Ellen! Get the bilge pump!
(Jake) Take the radio transmitter out
and hook it to the strobe.
- We gotta get the engine started!
- Just do it!
We're gonna feed that big boy
a meal he won't forget.
You better have something good going.
We've got a rotten hose.
There's a spare one.
What you wanna do with this?
I'm riggir the receiver. We get it
inside that bastard and set it off.
I got it. We rig an antenna on this.
we can shock the hell out of him.
Right! You're learning.
(Beating intensifies)
He's getting closer!
They spend their lives looking for
food. they don't care what it is.
Maybe he's got indigestion.
He's eaten my plane!
It's not food he's after.
Michael. turn on your switch.
I need a test.
- Anybody tell you you're nuts?
- All the time.
If it responds
to external electrical impulse.
it might respond to one inside -
confuse him. drive him crazy.
- (Electrical whine)
- 0K. a test... Good.
You'd better get up here!
The heartbeat's stopped!
Shit.
Either he's gone
or your gear's crapped out again.
That's bull. My equipment
don't crap out. He'll be back.
(Jake) Get me the boat hook.
(Hoagie) Maybe he had a heart attack.
Humans are full of cholesterol.
- Give me that.
- Shit! Where is he?
Give me that line. Michael.
Right there.
There he is!
(Hoagie) Ellen. try the engine.
Ellen! Try to start the engine!
(Engine starts)
Son of a bitch.
Let's get out of here.
No. it's too late. Hoagie.
Give me a hard port.
Right!
(Michael) Here. give me that.
(Jake) No! No time for that!
Jake! You can't go out there
without a line!
Keep it steady.
It's gonna come back!
Damn thing's disappeared. He's gone!
(Electronic heartbeat)
Jake!
We're taking too much water.
It'll stop the engine.
Ellen. take the wheel.
We've got to outrun it. Ellen!
- That thing gonna work?
- It'll work.
If Jake says so. it will.
This charge will drive it crazy.
(High-pitched drone)
(Roaring)
(Drone turns to patchy static)
Sweet Jesus.
we're headed straight for it!
Ellen. come about!
(Drone resumes)
(Roaring)
(Hoagie) We're gonna hit it!
Hold on!
Smile. you son of a bitch!
- Michael!
- Come over here.
Michael!
It's all right! I'm 0K!
(Man) Anybody there? 0ver here!
Jake!
Michael. you got a minute?
It's Jake!
Son of a bitch!
Jesus. Jake.
What took you so damn long. man?
What the hell are you doing alive?
I told you Uncle Jake's
equipment don't crap out. eh?
You're not going to do something
stupid like die on me. are you?
No. man. I'm way too mean for that.
So from now on.
we're going to study snails. eh?
Yeah.
(Ellen) Come to Amity this summer.
(Carla) We'll be there.
(Ellen) You make sure they come.
(Thea) I will.
I'll miss you. Grandma.
Get in. Ellen Brody.
You'll miss your plane.
- Goodbye. Grandma!
- 0K.
- Be careful.
- 0K. See ya.
- Take good care of Jake.
- I will.
You gonna be 0K?
- Yeah.
- 0K.
When I come back.
remind me to tell you about the time
I took a hundred nuns to Nairobi.
(Hoagie) There they were.
100 nuns. playing guitars
and singing. 'The hills are alive
with the sound of music.'
Then suddenly.
one comes up to me and she says.
'There's smoke coming
from the engine.'
But I never
took them seriously.
until they all started singing
'Nearer My God to Thee.'
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm